<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vegetarian on Yum Yum at TechNative</title><link>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/tags/vegetarian/</link><description>Recent content in vegetarian on Yum Yum at TechNative</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/tags/vegetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Indian vegan Curry with Naan v1.0</title><link>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/indian-curry-naan-v1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/indian-curry-naan-v1/</guid><description>1 Was de komkommer, halveer in de lengte en verwijder de zaadlijsten met een theelepel. Snijd het vruchtvlees in blokjes. Snipper de ui. Spoel de kikkererwten af onder koud stromend water en laat uitlekken.
2 Verhit de olie in een hapjespan en fruit de uien 2 min. op middelhoog vuur. Voeg de currypasta toe en fruit 2 min. mee. Voeg de kikkererwten, tomatenblokjes, komkommer en kokosmelk toe, breng aan de kook en kook het geheel in ca.</description></item><item><title>Mulligatawny soup</title><link>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/mulligatawny-soup-v1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/mulligatawny-soup-v1/</guid><description>A delicious comfort soup with a lot of veggies, herbs, and spices.
Preparation: Heat 2 tablespoons of ghee in a soup pot. Sauté the chopped onions and garlic. Finely chop the dried chili peppers. Add them to the pot along with the cumin seeds, crushed coriander seeds, mustard seeds, turmeric, and madras curry powder. Sauté for a moment. Add the cinnamon stick and grated fresh ginger. Sauté briefly. Rinse the lentils.</description></item><item><title>Okonomiyaki</title><link>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/okonomiyaki-v1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/okonomiyaki-v1/</guid><description>A Japanese streetfood dish
Preparation: Whisk the eggs in a bowl. Add the flour and whisk until you have a smooth batter. Add the soy sauce, ginger, Chinese cabbage, bean sprouts, spring onion, garlic, and carrot to the batter. Stir to combine. Season with salt and pepper. Heat a little rice oil in a frying pan. Pour half of the batter into the pan and cook the omelette on both sides until cooked through and golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Roasted marinated tofu with broccoli</title><link>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/roasted-marinated-tofu-with-broccoli-v1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wearetechnative.github.io/yumyum/recipe/roasted-marinated-tofu-with-broccoli-v1/</guid><description>An easy and delicious meal!
Preparation: Drain the tofu, wrap it in kitchen paper, and place something heavy on top to press out the moisture. Let it sit for at least 30 minutes. Mix the dark soy sauce, rice wine vinegar, brown sugar, ginger root, sriracha, sesame oil and garlic together in a large bowl. Remove the kitchen paper and cut the tofu into eight equal slices. Place them in the marinade and let them marinate for at least 30 minutes.</description></item></channel></rss>